[{"answer": "All I'm saying, before we take it down... maybe we should try it out.  You know. Christen the new house", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What do we need a bed for when we've got a fine shag carpet", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Do you have an appointment with us", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Actually, you do", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, it's Monday and first thing on Monday..", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Took care of what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, just the usual suspects. my friend says it's going to be a male bonding experience", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Hopefully, they'll all get drunk and crash early. Or if I'm really lucky... drown in the jacuzzi", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Would you rather I came to yours", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I know. I need help.  Help me, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come in. I'm sorry I'm such a mess but they won't let me take a shower or wash my hair.  Apparently I'm still on suicide watch", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well, still a bit groggy from the medication. But it isn't stopping me from feeling ashamed for all the trouble I've caused", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Goddamit, my friend, if there's an injured party here, it's me", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That's not going to happen because there's nothing to find out", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " You think I sent the flowers?   I'd have to be as crazy as she is", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "More", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I know", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'll go o", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What friend", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Nobody called me..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How are you", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I've missed you, too. Everything okay around the office", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's gonna be okay, honey.     We're gonna be oka", "docId": "Obsessed.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "And I love yo", "qsentId": 24}]